Hello friends,
you are very welcome inside SMD channel.  Friends,
in this video we will talk
about the shares of ICICI LB General Insurance Company.
As you can see on your screen
friends, today's date is 13th October.
Today we saw a negative trend in the stock.
Today we have seen a decline of more than 1.5%
in the stock and the final closing was seen at 1833.
Friends, I
want to give you important information.
Its quarter two results are going to be announced tomorrow i.e. on 14th October.
And friends,
this decline that we are seeing before the results
, somewhere it is also indicating
that the big operators probably have an
idea that we may see a good result
coming tomorrow.
So he is booking some profit.
First, they are
trying to make it cheaper from the upper level and at the cheaper
level, they have gradually
maintained their buying position here.
Friends, if we talk especially about option trading, because you
know that money is made very quickly in option trading.  So
by reducing its price,
we have also seen a position being created on the call side today.
So friends, if we get good results tomorrow, then
definitely
we will see a good upside move in it
and those who have
maintained their position on the call side in option trading will definitely get to
see good profits here.  But friends,
tomorrow we will come to know whether its results are
good or bad or
decent.
But friends, what will be our strategy
and what will be the important levels,
based on the results,
we will discuss about it in this video and
before moving ahead in the video, let us take a
look at the market cap of the company.
Friends, here we can see the market cap of Rs 920 crore.  The
company will soon touch this figure of Rs 1 lakh crore.  The PE
ratio is running at 34 which is at a decent level,
friends, at this time the face value also remains 10.
Friends, if we look at the profit, the
result of the last quarter one was quite
good.  A
profit of Rs 747 crore was recorded and
we saw a much better result compared to the profit of the previous quarter.  Now let's
see friends, tomorrow when this profit will come out, will it be
around 747, if there is
a little up or down then the result will be
considered decent.  If the result is very good
then there will definitely be a boom
and if it goes down a few points, that is, the
profit level goes down to 4050 crores on the
downside or
if the profit comes out below 700 crores, then
definitely friends, we will see selling from the top for once,
after that a bounce back will also come here
because friends, the company is
not a bad company, it is a very good company,
we can see its business also going very well,
apart from this, friends, the
promoter's stake here is 51%,
after that we can see the stake of FI and mutual funds here,
which is
indicating friends that we can
make this share a part of our portfolio according to our long term.
Now friends, we have come to the day chart.  First of all, let
us check our levels.  The
resistance level on the top is
1966 and then there is another resistance at 2038.
Both resistances together form our selling zone
or you can call it profit booking zone.  The
first support on the downside is 1787 then
1717.  We have two important support levels.
Apart from this, there is another support level
below which is 1638.  We will
not consider this right now.  Friends, if
we see very bad results then only
we will keep the support of 1638
in mind.  But for now, the
two upper support levels are a little more important for us
for tomorrow and the next few sessions.
Now friends,
as we can see on the day chart, the
share price is between its support and resistance,
although it is seen a little closer to the support.
So in such a situation, friends, if today or at a
lower level you have made a purchase on the
buying side, whether it is on the call side
for option trading or you have
bought shares normally, either for short term
or long term.
For the short term people, I
would like to tell friends if we get
to see good results then the levels of your profit
booking will be the upper
resistance level, when it goes near this level,
you can book profit and exit from the stock
and long term
friends whose outlook is a little longer, they
can comfortably maintain their position for the target of 2500 plus in the stock at least.  So friends, for the long term
people the target will be at least 2500
plus, after that we will talk friends when
it gives us the target of 2500 plus
and apart from that friends
if the result comes out to be decent,
neither good nor very bad, then
friends in such a situation
our 200 day moving average which
we are seeing near 1880 at this time.
If it tries to reach its 200-day moving average in the next few sessions, then
short-term investors can square off their positions here
because
from here, after facing resistance,
we can see it going down and
it will definitely reach its support again.  For
those who have
invested here for a very short period of time, the
200-day moving
average will be a very good level for
booking profit and exiting, but
we have to book profit from here only
when we see mixed results or decent levels,
and if
we see a decline in the stock, then
definitely we will see a decline here.
So in such a situation,
friends who want to do fresh buying, then for fresh
buying, our range between the first support and the second
support is the demand
range, when the stock comes in the middle of this demand range,
then we will take our position on the buying side and
move ahead.  If
friends who want to create their position for the long term,
then when 1787 comes near the first support, then
you can create your long term
position here and go ahead
and if someone
wants to create his position here for the short term, then
friends, if the decline increases a little and we
see this stock increasing and the
second support of 1717, we get to see this stock near this range
and in such a situation,
we get to see our RSI in the range of 25 to 35 and
we can also see any bullish candlestick pattern here,
suppose
if a hammer candlestick pattern is formed here, then
you can create your position here by taking your SL at the low of that candlestick pattern.
But SL guys you
can also take some points down.  According to this,
after your entry, you can keep your
target at 1 or 1:2 or
if you want to wait for two-three months, then you
can also keep your target close to the 200 day moving average.  Or if
you want to wait a little longer, then
you can consider your target and move till the resistance level above us.
Friends, long term investors can also adopt the same strategy and
create their buying side position.
But for them friends, the first
level to go to the buying side will be
1787.  If you feel that your
confidence is a little low near this level.  You might think there might be a
slight drop.  I am telling this for long term
people, friends.  If you
want to buy 100 shares in this stock, then
you can buy 25 to 50 shares
near the first support and the remaining
shares if
seen going down towards the second support.  You can
create your position here by averaging here.
So in this way you
can create your buying side position here.
And friends, those who have bought at the higher levels should
not panic at this time if we see a decline.
You can hold your position in this stock with a view of at least 4 to 6 months
or you can
also average it at a lower level.
Because friends, this
stock is a very good stock for the long term.  This can
definitely give you good returns in the future.
So, when there is a
fall, those who have bought from the upper level should
not feel any kind of problem because when we go to the lower level,
we will definitely see a bounce back from here.
So friends, this
was some information which I wanted to
share with you regarding the stock of the stock.
So if you liked the information given
in this video then
like the video and subscribe to the channel.
Thank you.